[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the gangster who intrudes upon the Fight Club meeting in the movie Fight Club?", "correct_answer": "Lou", "incorrect_answers": ["Tony", "Mikey", "Frank"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When a tornadoe warning is issued, you should get in your car and try to outrun the storm to get to safety.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following Solar System planets was not named after a Greek or Roman God?", "correct_answer": "Earth", "incorrect_answers": ["Mercury", "Saturn", "Uranus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the original name of the British rock band Sweet before they adopted their final name?", "correct_answer": "The Sweetshop", "incorrect_answers": ["Sugar and Spice", "Candy", "The Sugarcane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 2003 horror movie contains the following quote: Howdy Folks! You like blood? Violence? Freaks of nature? Well then, come on down to Captain Spauldings Museum of Monsters and Mad-Men.?", "correct_answer": "House of 1000 Corpses", "incorrect_answers": ["Planet Terror", "The Devils Rejects", "Halloween"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What planet has brown clouds floating over its surface?", "correct_answer": "Jupiter", "incorrect_answers": ["Neptune", "Uranus", "Saturn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "St Marks Basilica, a prominent example of Byzantine architecture, is located in which Italian city?", "correct_answer": "Venice", "incorrect_answers": ["Milan", "Rome", "Florence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The men of what religion wear the type of cap called taqiyah?", "correct_answer": "Islam", "incorrect_answers": ["Hinduism", "Buddhism", "Shintoism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are male hyenas the dominant members of their groups?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2004 movie Troy the following characters were killed in what order?", "correct_answer": "Menelaus, Hector, Priam, Achilles", "incorrect_answers": ["Hector, Priam, Menelaus, Achilles", "Hector, Priam, Achilles, Menelaus", "Priam, Hector, Menelaus, Achilles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Steel Magnolias, who does Annelle marry?", "correct_answer": "Sammy", "incorrect_answers": ["Harvey", "Tommy", "Spud"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is credited with the invention of the potato chip on August 24, 1853?", "correct_answer": "George Crum", "incorrect_answers": ["Rodger Alvarez", "Peter Queen", "Abraham Smith"]}]